day 32
I made the replacement here now of the truffles
guy and go ahead and stock up on the commercials
then put my new ideas out
now i am what
soon you will be on the third level in a little while
soon
good also is that when you level up
that your margin improves
with the same money you bought those truffles
i can buy more truffles
it's on then
12 sleeves 1 chestnut
Jump up
down
caraca captain of Novo
law of supply and demand
the secret is to find something that is good
but that person needs to see
oh i have the solution
oh i don't have that problem
i gotta have the right solution to the pain
customer's right
I will get to the places and sell my new service
from now on
the madman already
my god bro
I will keep more there
it's good my man
Lucas Arthur
it attracts you
brother money
yes and i have to understand your case
for us to be able to assemble something
really bagged
i'm putting on a skill that i know
deliver
it's bro clean the window and get all blurry
it was more for the money
thank you brother
tamo together
pear pear girl
ran out of truffles
brother caraca
the truffle so flying crazy
the base I'm rolling on the Trojan horse
it's helping me to have this peace of mind
because if I had very little
money and i speak
caramba
ferrou bro
it's raining again
I'll have to clean up shop window
we can't stay in the rain
how am i going to sell in the rain
I'm trying to prospect New business
but the truffles are old Rolando
EU I get 1 customer
I know I get 2
I get 2
I get 4
and then it was
okay
good my dear
fall only in rigid hours
it's nothing
I guess I was thinking about this this week
hand the differentiation point
we can put authenticity in family food
to be the market differential
that's where I come in
does the following
takes a test
result
maybe through that
may be more interesting
for your communication
five i buy this idea a lot bro
she'll be pretty cool in the hour bro
hope you liked it
man let's close that tape there
took a while
took a while for me
is closed
tamo together
sold the idea
gave a certain hand
ah still won marmitex and a pussy zero
my brother
good thing
1 1 that you get right is worth more than 30
40 things you're doing
until tomorrow people
good night
I'll eat this here
Up up down
Jump up
Jump up and get down